blufin.it 2019-02-03

# AllAboutCookies.org Privacy and Cookie Policy

Welcome To All About Cookies.org

Our Privacy Policy

We at AllAboutCookies.org take privacy of our visitors seriously and we wish to stress that we do not gather, save, collect nor use any personal information of visitors to our Website.

Statistic Programmes and Cookie Policy 

We employ our own customised statistic analytics which uses [session cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/session-cookies-used-for.html) that expire after each session which we use to identify what country you visit from, what methods and how you come to visit our site, including whether you came direct to our site or from another website and the [URL](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uniform_Resource_Locator) of that website.We also try to identify if you have visited us from a search engine such as Google or Bing and for what search string you used, or whether it was from a bookmark.We also follow and note the pages you visit. We do not usually collect nor store the [Internet protocol address](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/faqs/) (IP) from which you visit. However, for security reasons, we may at time turn on our log analyser, to ascertain, where a attempted security breach is taking place and that will log IP's.

The information generated by our first party cookies about your use of our website is stored by us on a server in the United States of America.The data is kept for a maximum of 30 days and then deleted. No data is shared or given to third parties.These cookies DO NOT identify, you, nor do they store personal information, but just the action of your use of our website. We also have a cookie, that remembers your acceptance of our cookie policy.This cookie expires after 30 days. So in summary, here are our 2 cookies and their function

Cookies we use

Cookie Name | Cookie Expires After | Cookie Function  
---|---|---  
PHPSESSID | Immediately | Strictly for statistical purposes, to track and monitor, what country, what pages and what method, was used to visit the site.See above for more details  
Cookiescriptaccept |  30 days | 

To remember your cookie acceptance.Cookie acceptance is implied after 60 seconds of staying on the site.  
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, refer the [manage cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/) section of this site. 

Third Party Advertising and their Cookie Policy

To pay for the running and publishing of the site, we use google's Adsense program to serve ads when you visit our website.Our site would not exist without advertisers paying to put their ads on this site.

Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, click here.[https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

Email Policy

AllAboutCookies.org does not collect, sell, rent, or otherwise distribute email addresses or any other personal information. We also do not solicit or collect any emails unless you make a request for reuse of our content or advertising enquiries or other general enquiry. All discussions by email or phone are completely confidential unless we obtain written consent from you.

Please Note

Our Privacy Policy is subject to change.We will mark any change by placing a asterix * beside our link to our Policy.

This policy was last updated 30th September 2015
